Guide to the J. Walter Thompson Company. New York Office. Media Center Audiovisual Collection, 1953-2015 and undated RL.00734
David M. Rubenstein Rare Book & Manuscript Library
- Audio Materials, 1953-2000; undated; 2
  - Stever Aubrey, New Business Department, 1966 (Box A10, Audio-reel RL00734-RR-083)
  - Ted Landfair, The Plague Nobody Wants, WMAL Consumer Affairs Special, Undated (Box A10, Audio-reel RL00734-RR-084)
  - Ted Wilson, Fred Ronai, K. Robbins, The Function of the Representative, 1965 (Box A10, Audio-reel RL00734-RR-085)
  - Tom Sutton et al, reel 1, 1969 (Box A10, Audio-reel RL00734-RR-086)
  - Tom Sutton, Peter Dunham, Jack Webster, Richard Vorce, The World of JWT, 1963 (Box A10, Audio-reel RL00734-RR-087)
  - Trailways PR Presentation, 1958 (Box A10, Audio-reel RL00734-RR-088)
  - Untitled reel 2, Undated (Box A10, Audio-reel RL00734-RR-089)
  - Untitled reel 1, Undated (Box A10, Audio-reel RL00734-RR-090)
  - Wally Clayton, Champion Spark Plug Story, 1961 (Box A10, Audio-reel RL00734-RR-091)
  - Wally O'Brien, #1 Seminar, 1962 (Box A10, Audio-reel RL00734-RR-092)
  - Wallace Elton, Nan Findlow, Helen Klintrup, Robert Colwell Editorial Seminar panel, 1961 (Box A10, Audio-reel RL00734-RR-093)
  - 1st Hour Luncheon, 1963 (Box A10, Audio-reel RL00734-RR-094)
  - Dan Seymour, Undated (Box A10, Audio-reel RL00734-RR-095)
  - Don Thorbam, Sidney Bernstein interview, 1963 (Box A10, Audio-reel RL00734-RR-096)
  - Ed Robinson, Sidney Bernstein interview, Undated (Box A10, Audio-reel RL00734-RR-097)
  - Henderson Luncheon, Arno Johnson, Howard Kohl, Wilson Seibert, Milt Moscowitz, Sidney Bernstein, M. Keating, 1963 (Box A10, Audio-reel RL00734-RR-098)
  - Henry Flower, Greenwich Conn., Undated (Box A10, Audio-reel RL00734-RR-099)
  - Howard Kohl, Sidney Bernstein in Kohn office, 1964 (Box A10, Audio-reel RL00734-RR-100)
  - James Webb Young, Sidney Bernstein, 1963 (Box A10, Audio-reel RL00734-RR-101)
  - James Webb Young, I Knew J. Walter Thompson, 1962 (Box A10, Audio-reel RL00734-RR-102)
  - Jen Donaldson (Advertising Manager, Ford), 1964 (Box A10, Audio-reel RL00734-RR-103)
  - John Devine, Sidney Bernstein, 1964 (Box A10, Audio-reel RL00734-RR-104)
  - M. Tempest, 1963 (Box A10, Audio-reel RL00734-RR-105)
  - Nancy Stephenson, Sidney Bernstein interview, 1963 (Box A10, Audio-reel RL00734-RR-106)
  - Norman Strouse tape 2, 1963 (Box A10, Audio-reel RL00734-RR-107)
  - Norman Strouse, Sidney Bernstein interview, Undated (Box A10, Audio-reel RL00734-RR-108)
  - Norman Strouse, Sidney Bernstein interview, 1964 (Box A10, Audio-reel RL00734-RR-109)
  - Norman Strouse, Sidney Bernstein interview, 1964 (Box A10, Audio-reel RL00734-RR-110)
  - Norman Strouse, Sidney Bernstein interview, Undated (Box A10, Audio-reel RL00734-RR-111)
  - O'Neill Ryan, 1963 (Box A10, Audio-reel RL00734-RR-112)
  - O'Neill Ryan, 1963 (Box A10, Audio-reel RL00734-RR-113)
  - Peggy King, Undated (Box A10, Audio-reel RL00734-RR-114)
  - Phil Nygatt, Sidney Bernstein interview, 1964 (Box A10, Audio-reel RL00734-RR-115)
  - Ruth Waldo, 1964 (Box A10, Audio-reel RL00734-RR-116)
  - Sam Meek 1st tape, Undated (Box A10, Audio-reel RL00734-RR-117)
  - Sam Meek 2nd tape, Undated (Box A11, Audio-reel RL00734-RR-118)
  - Sidney Bernstein, James Webb Young, 1963 (Box A11, Audio-reel RL00734-RR-119)
  - Walter O'Meara, Robert Colwell in Colwell Office, 1963 (Box A11, Audio-reel RL00734-RR-120)
  - (Alvin) Achenbaum-(William) Ross, Tarrytown Seminar, Concerns of Management, 1972 (Box A11, Audio-reel RL00734-RR-121)
  - Ballad of Kennett Hinks, Undated (Box A11, Audio-reel RL00734-RR-122)
  - Bernard Owett, Ruth Downing, Three Advertising Problems, Undated (Box A11, Audio-reel RL00734-RR-123)
  - Dave Garroway notes, Undated (Box A11, Audio-reel RL00734-RR-124)
  - Edward Durrell Stone, Stone's Don'ts, 1961 (Box A11, Audio-reel RL00734-RR-125)
  - Fickinger Harris, JWT Seminar, Concerns of Management, 1972 (Box A11, Audio-reel RL00734-RR-126)
  - Food and Drug Administration, Toy Safety Program spots, 1972 (Box A11, Audio-reel RL00734-RR-127)
  - Ford, BB 5467, 1959 (Box A11, Audio-reel RL00734-RR-128)
  - Ford Billboard opening, closing, Undated (Box A11, Audio-reel RL00734-RR-129)
  - Ford Startime Music Themes, NBC Hollywood, 1959 (Box A11, Audio-reel RL00734-RR-130)
  - Fred Kittell, Art Department, 1964 (Box A11, Audio-reel RL00734-RR-131)
  - JWT Music Experience--Music created by JWT Chicago for its clients, Undated (Box A11, Audio-reel RL00734-RR-132)
  - Norman Strouse re JWT going public, 1969 (Box A11, Audio-reel RL00734-RR-133)
  - Professional Perspectives, 1965 (Box A11, Audio-reel RL00734-RR-134)
  - Robertson-(Denis) Lanigan, Tarrytown Seminar, Concerns of Management, 1972 (Box A11, Audio-reel RL00734-RR-135)
  - Road West copy from 35mm optical, Undated (Box A11, Audio-reel RL00734-RR-136)
  - Road West main title music master, Undated (Box A11, Audio-reel RL00734-RR-137)
  - Road West Sonoscope master, Undated (Box A11, Audio-reel RL00734-RR-138)
  - Sam Meek, 85th birthday messages, John Humphries, Martin O'Grady, Sir John Rogers, Sandy Mitchell-Innes, Dennis Scott (JWT London), 1980 (Box A11, Audio-reel RL00734-RR-139)
  - Security Analysts Meeting Q&A with Don Johnston, 1978 (Box A11, Audio-reel RL00734-RR-140)
  - Untitled, Undated (Box A11, Audio-reel RL00734-RR-141)
  - William Hinks, JWT London, 1962 (Box A11, Audio-reel RL00734-RR-142)
  - Wyatte Hicks, Tarrytown Seminar, Concerns of Management, 1972 (Box A11, Audio-reel RL00734-RR-143)
  - Ford auditions, Undated (Box A12, Audio-reel RL00734-RR-144)
  - Ford commercials, Bee Swap, Undated (Box A12, Audio-reel RL00734-RR-145)
  - Ford Startime, 1959 (Box A12, Audio-reel RL00734-RR-146)
  - Ford Startime, 1959 (Box A12, Audio-reel RL00734-RR-147)
  - Ford Theme long version, tag, reel 1-a, Undated (Box A12, Audio-reel RL00734-RR-148)
  - Ford Theme long version, tag, reel 1-b, Undated (Box A13, Audio-reel RL00734-RR-149)
  - Schlitz radio spots, 1959 (Box A13, Audio-reel RL00734-RR-150)
  - Tennessee Ernie Ford commercials, Swapping Bee, 1961 (Box A13, Audio-reel RL00734-RR-151)
  - Wong's Frozen Chinese Foods, 1953 (Box A13, Audio-reel RL00734-RR-152)
  - 1966 Christmas Chorus. New York Office Choral Group. FR-1682. 10 inch, 33 1/3 RPM. (Box P1, Audio-phonodisc RL00734-PD-001)
  - 1966 Christmas Chorus. New York Office Choral Group. FR-1682. 10 inch, 33 1/3 RPM. (Box P1, Audio-phonodisc RL00734-PD-002)
  - Cash in with STP. Includes Johnny Cash "! Would Like to See You Again". Columbia KC-35313. 12 inch, 33 1/3 RPM., 1978 (Box P1, Audio-phonodisc RL00734-PD-003)
  - Chase and Sanborn 101st Anniversary Show. SR4M-3328. 12 inch, 33 1/3 RPM, 1965 (Box P1, Audio-phonodisc RL00734-PD-004)
  - J. Walter Thompson Company 16th Annual Crystal Ball Dinner souvenir program. MO8P-3092. 12 inch, 33 1/3 RPM, 1961 (Box P1, Audio-phonodisc RL00734-PD-005)
  - JWT Argentina. Villancicos Latinoamericanos. Coro polifonico J. Walter Thompson Argentina. 12 inch, 33 1/3 RPM, 1966 (Box P1, Audio-phonodisc RL00734-PD-006)
  - JWT San Francisco. The Christmas Sounds of San Francisco. SF-2489. 10 inch, 33 1/3 RPM., Undated (Box P1, Audio-phonodisc RL00734-PD-007)
  - JWT South Africa. Some of the Greatest Hits of J. Walter Thompson: A Selection of Radio Commercials. 7 inch, 45 RPM, Undated (Box P1, Audio-phonodisc RL00734-PD-008)
  - JWT Vienna. Johann Strauss 100th Anniversary Concert Produced by J. Walter Thompson Vienna. Decca SX-21178. An Der Schonen Blauen Donau. Wiener Philharmoniker. 12 inch, 33 1/3 RPM., 1975 (Box P1, Audio-phonodisc RL00734-PD-009)
  - Kraft 75th Anniversary Radio Special. KARS 0075. 12 inch, 33 1/3 RPM, 1978 (Box P1, Audio-phonodisc RL00734-PD-010)
  - Oscar Mayer/JWT Celebrating 20 Years of Harmony. Meatpacker Suite b/w The Flying Dutchman by Richard Wagner. University of Wisconsin Symphony Orchestra, Catherine Comet conductor. 12 inch, 33 1/3 RPM, 1980 (Box P1, Audio-phonodisc RL00734-PD-011)
  - Stan Bush. Forever extended version b/w Blinded; Forever single version. CBS 655848. 12 inch, 45 RPM, 1990 (Box P1, Audio-phonodisc RL00734-PD-012)
- Film, 1957-1974; undated; 3
  - Comedy Ice-Breaker film 15 min., Undated (Box F1, Film-reel RL00734-F16-001)
  - Ford Dealer Association, Dick Van Dyke, 1974 (Box F1, Film-reel RL00734-F16-002)
  - JWT (New York) Christmas tape, Dan Seymour voiceover, Undated (Box F1, Film-reel RL00734-F16-003)
  - JWT (Chicago) funny tour reel, Undated (Box F1, Film-reel RL00734-F16-004)
  - JWT Japan: Pond's, Kodak, Scott Tissue, TWS, Kellogg's, Lux, Pepsi, Dentyne, 1969 (Box F1, Film-reel RL00734-F16-005)
  - JWT-NY 60 celebration, Norman Strouse, Undated (Box F1, Film-reel RL00734-F16-006)
  - Marlboro Cigarettes, Undated (Box F1, Film-reel RL00734-F16-007)
  - Singer/Burt Bacharach Case History #2, Undated (Box F1, Film-reel RL00734-F16-008)
  - Tip Top Bread, Aluminum Ltd., 7-Up spots, circa 1959 (Box F1, Film-reel RL00734-F16-009)
  - Milton Berle 2022, Undated (Box F1, Film-reel RL00734-F16-010)
  - Milton Berle 1886, 10 sec., Undated (Box F1, Film-reel RL00734-F16-011)
  - Milton Berle 1885, 10 sec., Undated (Box F1, Film-reel RL00734-F16-012)
  - Milton Berle 1884, 10 sec., Undated (Box F1, Film-reel RL00734-F16-013)
  - Trailways 4106 introduction, Silver Anniversary Fleet, Undated (Box F1, Film-reel RL00734-F16-014)
  - Trailways Bus "Five Star", 1960 (Box F1, Film-reel RL00734-F16-015)
  - Trailways delivery and introduction of 4106 model, Undated (Box F1, Film-reel RL00734-F16-016)
  - Trailways Doll, Northeastern Cities, 1960 (Box F1, Film-reel RL00734-F16-017)
  - Trailways Doll, Southeastern Cities, 1960 (Box F1, Film-reel RL00734-F16-018)
  - Trailways Girl with Doll, Undated (Box F1, Film-reel RL00734-F16-019)
  - Trailways footage of 4106 model, Undated (Box F1, Film-reel RL00734-F16-020)
  - Trailways Santa Claus, 1957 (Box F1, Film-reel RL00734-F16-021)
  - Trailways Silver Fleet, 1962 (Box F1, Film-reel RL00734-F16-022)
  - Trailways Talking Bus, Undated (Box F1, Film-reel RL00734-F16-023)
  - Untitled, Undated (Box F1, Film-reel RL00734-F16-024)
  - WXEY-TV Richmond, Undated (Box F1, Film-reel RL00734-F16-025)
  - Ford Marketing Corp., A Car Is Born, 26:30 for TV projection, Undated (Box F2, Film-reel RL00734-F16-026)
  - Mrs. America, Trailways version, Undated (Box F2, Film-reel RL00734-F16-027)
  - Trailways, Baltimore terminal in construction, circa 1959 (Box F2, Film-reel RL00734-F16-028)
  - Trailways, construction of terminal TV spot, circa 1959 (Box F2, Film-reel RL00734-F16-029)
  - Trailways, Go Trailways, circa 1959 (Box F2, Film-reel RL00734-F16-030)
  - Trailways, Mrs. America (also sponsored by Lux, RCA, Rit Dye, Singer), 1959 (Box F2, Film-reel RL00734-F16-031)
  - Trailways, Mrs. America, 1960 (Box F2, Film-reel RL00734-F16-032)
  - Trailways, Miami Trailways terminal improvement program, circa 1959 (Box F2, Film-reel RL00734-F16-033)
  - Trailways, Willie Takes a Trip (film for employees), Undated (Box F2, Film-reel RL00734-F16-034)
- Optical Media (CDs, DVDs), 1993-2015; undated; 4
  - 60 Minutes: The Millennials Are Coming, 2007 (Box O1, Optical-disc RL00734-OP-0001)
  - @JWT: 7 Immutable Laws, 2015 (Box O1, Optical-disc RL00734-OP-0002)
  - AAAA (American Association of Advertising Agencies): Agency Ideas and Work--Rights, Ownership, Usage, Intellectual Property and Compensation, 2008 (Box O1, Optical-disc RL00734-OP-0003)
  - AAAA (American Association of Advertising Agencies): Agency Ideas and Work--Rights, Ownership, Usage, Intellectual Property and Compensation, 2008 (Box O1, Optical-disc RL00734-OP-0004)
  - Advanced Brand Communications workshop presentations, Undated (Box O1, Optical-disc RL00734-OP-0005)
  - Advanced Brand Communications workshop presentations, Undated (Box O1, Optical-disc RL00734-OP-0006)
  - Ali Asani, Undated (Box O1, Optical-disc RL00734-OP-0007)
  - All Employees pictures, 2008 (Box O1, Optical-disc RL00734-OP-0008)
  - Asia Pacific--1998 2nd quarter print ads (Box O1, Optical-disc RL00734-OP-0009)
  - Asia Pacific--1998 3rd quarter print review (Box O1, Optical-disc RL00734-OP-0010)
  - Asia Pacific--1998 4th quarter, 1999 (Box O1, Optical-disc RL00734-OP-0011)
  - Asia Pacific--1998 4th quarter, 1999 (Box O1, Optical-disc RL00734-OP-0012)
  - Asia Pacific--1998 Yearly Creative Standards, 1999 (Box O1, Optical-disc RL00734-OP-0013)
  - Asia Pacific--1999 print ads, 2000 (Box O1, Optical-disc RL00734-OP-0014)
  - Asia Pacific--EXCO print ads, 1998 (Box O1, Optical-disc RL00734-OP-0015)
  - Augusta National Golf Club, Stephen Szurlej, Undated (Box O1, Optical-disc RL00734-OP-0016)
  - Australia--Melbourne November Update, 2007 (Box O1, Optical-disc RL00734-OP-0017)
  - Australia--Melbourne November Update, 2007 (Box O1, Optical-disc RL00734-OP-0018)
  - Barry Diller, for Dinner, IAC Highlight Reel, Undated (Box O1, Optical-disc RL00734-OP-0019)
  - Ben Gregor--Cannes Contenders Video Game Ads, 2011 (Box O1, Optical-disc RL00734-OP-0020)
  - Billions--Tom Doctoroff press kit, Undated (Box O1, Optical-disc RL00734-OP-0021)
  - Bob Jeffrey--10th anniversary, 2008 (Box O1, Optical-disc RL00734-OP-0022)
  - Bob Jeffrey--Keynote at Digitrends, Undated (Box O1, Optical-disc RL00734-OP-0023)
  - Bob Jeffrey--Presentation at Digitrends, 2001 (Box O1, Optical-disc RL00734-OP-0024)
  - Bob Jeffrey--Presentation to London and Latin American Offices, 2004 (Box O1, Optical-disc RL00734-OP-0025)
  - Bob Woodruff Foundation--ReMIND.org, 2009 (Box O1, Optical-disc RL00734-OP-0026)
  - Bob Woodruff Foundation--ReMIND.org, 2009 (Box O1, Optical-disc RL00734-OP-0027)
  - Cannes--CNBC TV18, 2005 (Box O1, Optical-disc RL00734-OP-0028)
  - Cannes--Film Grand Prix, Gold Silver and Bronze Lions, 2006 (Box O1, Optical-disc RL00734-OP-0029)
  - Cannes--Lions winners, 2008 (Box O1, Optical-disc RL00734-OP-0030)
  - Cannes--Lions, 2009 (Box O1, Optical-disc RL00734-OP-0031)
  - Cannes--Lions, 2010 (Box O1, Optical-disc RL00734-OP-0032)
  - Cannes--Lions, 2010 (Box O1, Optical-disc RL00734-OP-0033)
  - Cannes--Lions, 2012 (Box O1, Optical-disc RL00734-OP-0034)
  - Cannes--Lions, 2012 (Box O1, Optical-disc RL00734-OP-0035)
  - Cannes--Lions, 2012 (Box O1, Optical-disc RL00734-OP-0036)
  - Cannes--Photos, 2005 (Box O1, Optical-disc RL00734-OP-0037)
  - Cannes--Photos, 2005 (Box O1, Optical-disc RL00734-OP-0038)
  - Cannes--Photos, 2005 (Box O1, Optical-disc RL00734-OP-0039)
  - Cannes--Photos, 2005 (Box O1, Optical-disc RL00734-OP-0040)
  - Cannes--Photos, 2007 (Box O1, Optical-disc RL00734-OP-0041)
  - Cannes--Photos 2, Undated (Box O1, Optical-disc RL00734-OP-0042)
  - Cannes--Winners (JetBlue, Sundance), 2006 (Box O2, Optical-disc RL00734-OP-0043)
  - Clearing the Air (Shell), 2008 (Box O2, Optical-disc RL00734-OP-0044)
  - Cosmo Street--Smirnoff People's Challenge Web Video, 2010 (Box O2, Optical-disc RL00734-OP-0045)
  - Cosmo Street--Smirnoff People's Challenge Web Video, 2010 (Box O2, Optical-disc RL00734-OP-0046)
  - Cosmo Street--Smirnoff Documentary, 2010 (Box O2, Optical-disc RL00734-OP-0047)
  - deja vu, Undated (Box O2, Optical-disc RL00734-OP-0048)
  - Diamond Trading Company, 2007 (Box O2, Optical-disc RL00734-OP-0049)
  - Diamond Trading Company--Diamonds: A Piece of Eternity, 2006 (Box O2, Optical-disc RL00734-OP-0050)
  - European Creative League, Undated (Box O2, Optical-disc RL00734-OP-0051)
  - Faith Popcorn's Brain Reserve Recession Survey, 2008 (Box O2, Optical-disc RL00734-OP-0052)
  - Focus Group--jwt.com UX research, 2011 (Box O2, Optical-disc RL00734-OP-0053)
  - Ford--Ford Asia Pacific and Mazda Creative, 2007 (Box O2, Optical-disc RL00734-OP-0054)
  - Ford--Bold Moves.com, Undated (Box O2, Optical-disc RL00734-OP-0055)
  - Ford--Bold Moves Tri-State Ford Dealer spots, 2006 (Box O2, Optical-disc RL00734-OP-0056)
  - Ford--Broadcast creative, 2005 (Box O2, Optical-disc RL00734-OP-0057)
  - Ford--F-150 case study, 2005 (Box O2, Optical-disc RL00734-OP-0058)
  - Ford--Freestyle spots, Undated (Box O2, Optical-disc RL00734-OP-0059)
  - Ford--International television spots, 2005 (Box O2, Optical-disc RL00734-OP-0060)
  - Ford--It's Not Just a New Truck It's the All New '09 F-150, 2008 (Box O2, Optical-disc RL00734-OP-0061)
  - Ford--Team Detroit Brand Content and Alliance, 2005 (Box O2, Optical-disc RL00734-OP-0062)
  - Ford--Team Detroit Fiesta Movement, 2010 (Box O2, Optical-disc RL00734-OP-0063)
  - Ford--Team Detroit Ford Proving Grounds, 2008 (Box O2, Optical-disc RL00734-OP-0064)
  - Ford--Tri-State Ford Dealers Derek Jeter spots, 2008 (Box O2, Optical-disc RL00734-OP-0065)
  - K-Post DeBeers compilation, 2007 (Box O2, Optical-disc RL00734-OP-0066)
  - From Interruption to Engagement, Undated (Box O2, Optical-disc RL00734-OP-0067)
  - G/J "Graves", Undated (Box O2, Optical-disc RL00734-OP-0068)
  - Germany--Aus der Timotei Werbung; Beautiful World In the Beginning, 1993 (Box O2, Optical-disc RL00734-OP-0069)
  - Global Agency of the Year, 2010 (Box O2, Optical-disc RL00734-OP-0070)
  - Go Robot--Whoo! Alright Yeah Uh Huh, 2007 (Box O2, Optical-disc RL00734-OP-0071)
  - HSBC, Undated (Box O2, Optical-disc RL00734-OP-0072)
  - HSBC--Barcelona, Undated (Box O2, Optical-disc RL00734-OP-0073)
  - HSBC--Craig, 2007 (Box O2, Optical-disc RL00734-OP-0074)
  - HSBC--Print Ads (Spanish), 2006 (Box O2, Optical-disc RL00734-OP-0075)
  - iTunes 1, Undated (Box O2, Optical-disc RL00734-OP-0076)
  - iTunes 2, Undated (Box O2, Optical-disc RL00734-OP-0077)
  - iTunes 3, Undated (Box O2, Optical-disc RL00734-OP-0078)
  - iTunes 4, Undated (Box O2, Optical-disc RL00734-OP-0079)
  - iTunes 5, Undated (Box O2, Optical-disc RL00734-OP-0080)
  - Johannes Leonardo--Nomis, Pangea Day, Undated (Box O2, Optical-disc RL00734-OP-0081)
  - JWT DVD--Ford International, Undated (Box O2, Optical-disc RL00734-OP-0082)
  - JWT DVD--Ford Domestic, Undated (Box O2, Optical-disc RL00734-OP-0083)
  - JWT DVD--Tom Cordner General Reel and Lexus Work, Undated (Box O2, Optical-disc RL00734-OP-0084)
  - JWT DVD--Michael Maedel and Lew Trencher video of presentation, Undated (Box O2, Optical-disc RL00734-OP-0085)
  - JWT DVD--Rosemarie Ryan video of presentation, Undated (Box O2, Optical-disc RL00734-OP-0086)
  - JWT DVD--New JWT Launch JWT Corporate ID intro video, Undated (Box O2, Optical-disc RL00734-OP-0087)
  - JWT DVD--New JWT Launch Commodore opening video, Undated (Box O2, Optical-disc RL00734-OP-0088)
  - JWT Halloween party, 2009 (Box O2, Optical-disc RL00734-OP-0089)
  - JWT photos, Undated (Box O2, Optical-disc RL00734-OP-0090)
  - JWT Seminar Cannes Lions, 2006 (Box O2, Optical-disc RL00734-OP-0091)
  - JWT TV compilation--Smirnoff, Shell, Nike, Sedal, HSBC, Halls, Kit Kat, NicoDerm, MTV, Knorr, Lux, 2007 (Box O2, Optical-disc RL00734-OP-0092)
  - JWT TV compilation--Smirnoff, Shell, Nike, Sedal, HSBC, Halls, Kit Kat, NicoDerm, MTV, Knorr, Lux, 2007 (Box O2, Optical-disc RL00734-OP-0093)
  - JWT Spring Reel Quicktime and AVI, 2000 (Box O3, Optical-disc RL00734-OP-0094)
  - JWT State of the Agency and party pictures, 2003 (Box O3, Optical-disc RL00734-OP-0095)
  - JWTwo--ABC Nightly News with Charles Gibson, 2008 (Box O3, Optical-disc RL00734-OP-0096)
  - JWTwo--Adweek 30th Anniversary; Bob Jeffrey, Gary Goldsmith, 2008 (Box O3, Optical-disc RL00734-OP-0097)
  - JWTwo--Adweek Report Card 2007, 2008 (Box O3, Optical-disc RL00734-OP-0098)
  - JWTwo--Agency of the Year Submission, 2008 (Box O3, Optical-disc RL00734-OP-0099)
  - JWTwo--America's Nightly Scoreboard: Guest Bob Jeffrey, 2008 (Box O3, Optical-disc RL00734-OP-0100)
  - JWTwo--Ann Mack America's Nightly Scoreboard, 2008 (Box O3, Optical-disc RL00734-OP-0101)
  - JWTwo--Barack Obama Inauguration part 1, 2009 (Box O3, Optical-disc RL00734-OP-0102)
  - JWTwo--Barack Obama Inauguration part 2, 2009 (Box O3, Optical-disc RL00734-OP-0103)
  - JWTwo--Battle of the Bands, 2011 (Box O3, Optical-disc RL00734-OP-0104)
  - JWTwo--BBC, 2007 (Box O3, Optical-disc RL00734-OP-0105)
  - JWTwo--BBC, 2007 (Box O3, Optical-disc RL00734-OP-0106)
  - JWTwo--Beta-7 3:18, 2007 (Box O3, Optical-disc RL00734-OP-0107)
  - JWTwo--Beta-7 11:10, 2007 (Box O3, Optical-disc RL00734-OP-0108)
  - JWTwo--BIEB Case Study data disk, 2010 (Box O3, Optical-disc RL00734-OP-0109)
  - JWTwo--BIEB Case Study data dvd, 2010 (Box O3, Optical-disc RL00734-OP-0110)
  - JWTwo--Billy Collins screen grabs, 2007 (Box O3, Optical-disc RL00734-OP-0111)
  - JWTwo--Bing and Decide Effies Submission Video, 2009 (Box O3, Optical-disc RL00734-OP-0112)
  - JWTwo--Bob Jeffrey Adweek Global Award Announcement, 2010 (Box O3, Optical-disc RL00734-OP-0113)
  - JWTwo--Bob Jeffrey America's Nightly Scoreboard, Remind.org, 2008 (Box O3, Optical-disc RL00734-OP-0114)
  - JWTwo--Bob Jeffrey Bloomberg TV, 2007 (Box O3, Optical-disc RL00734-OP-0115)
  - JWTwo--Bob Jeffrey Brown University suporting materials, 2009 (Box O3, Optical-disc RL00734-OP-0116)
  - JWTwo--Bob Jeffrey Brown University talk, 2008 (Box O3, Optical-disc RL00734-OP-0117)
  - JWTwo--Bob Jeffrey Nokia Digital Pitch Laptop Videos, 2008 (Box O3, Optical-disc RL00734-OP-0118)
  - JWTwo--Bob Jeffrey Presentation Media 30:00, 2008 (Box O3, Optical-disc RL00734-OP-0119)
  - JWTwo--Bob Jeffrey Presentation Media :30, 2008 (Box O3, Optical-disc RL00734-OP-0120)
  - JWTwo--Bob Woodruff Foundation remind.org video 1, 2009 (Box O3, Optical-disc RL00734-OP-0121)
  - JWTwo--Bolt.com 26 spots, 2008 (Box O3, Optical-disc RL00734-OP-0122)
  - JWTwo--Bubblicious 2005-2007, 2008 (Box O3, Optical-disc RL00734-OP-0123)
  - JWTwo--Burger King spots, 2008 (Box O3, Optical-disc RL00734-OP-0124)
  - JWTwo--Business Week Video Newsmakers; Marian Salzman, 2007 (Box O3, Optical-disc RL00734-OP-0125)
  - JWTwo--C3 Global Creative Showcase 2009, 2010 (Box O3, Optical-disc RL00734-OP-0126)
  - JWTwo--Cadbury Adams, Stride "Tick Tock", 2008 (Box O3, Optical-disc RL00734-OP-0127)
  - JWTwo--Cadbury Gorilla, 2008 (Box O3, Optical-disc RL00734-OP-0128)
  - JWTwo--Cannes Bieb case study :60, 2010 (Box O3, Optical-disc RL00734-OP-0129)
  - JWTwo--Cannes edits, 2008 (Box O3, Optical-disc RL00734-OP-0130)
  - JWTwo--Cannes Lions 2010: Winners Film Craft Lions, Jury special awards disc 2 (Box O3, Optical-disc RL00734-OP-0131)
  - JWTwo--Cannes Lions 2010: Winners Film Lions Young Lions Winners, jury special awards disc 1 (Box O3, Optical-disc RL00734-OP-0132)
  - JWTwo--Cannes Lions 2010: Winners Direct, Media, Promo, Activation disc 4 (Box O3, Optical-disc RL00734-OP-0133)
  - JWTwo--Cannes Lions 2010: Winners Press, Outdoor, Radio, Titanium and Integrated disc 3 (Box O3, Optical-disc RL00734-OP-0134)
  - JWTwo--Case creative, Brazilian presentation to Martin Sorrell, 2008 (Box O3, Optical-disc RL00734-OP-0135)
  - JWTwo--CBS Sunday Morning, Office Chair Story, Undated (Box O3, Optical-disc RL00734-OP-0136)
  - JWTwo--CBS Sunday Morning News with Charles Osgood, Bob Jeffrey talking about advertising and Super Bowl, 2010 (Box O3, Optical-disc RL00734-OP-0137)
  - JWTwo--CBS Ten Greatest Super Bowl Ads of All Time, 2010 (Box O3, Optical-disc RL00734-OP-0138)
  - JWTwo--Chicago Dibs campaign work, 2008 (Box O3, Optical-disc RL00734-OP-0139)
  - JWTwo--Christmas spots for presentation, 2007 (Box O3, Optical-disc RL00734-OP-0140)
  - JWTwo--Colleen Higgins presentation, 2008 (Box O3, Optical-disc RL00734-OP-0141)
  - JWTwo--Colorshowdown.com, 2008 (Box O3, Optical-disc RL00734-OP-0142)
  - JWTwo--Consumer Alignment Meeting, 2007 (Box O3, Optical-disc RL00734-OP-0143)
  - JWTwo--Creative Solutions, 2008 (Box O3, Optical-disc RL00734-OP-0144)
  - JWTwo--Creative Work EXCO April, 2010 (Box O3, Optical-disc RL00734-OP-0145)
  - JWTwo--DeBeers Diamond Is Forever Times Square Shoot, 2006 (Box O3, Optical-disc RL00734-OP-0146)
  - JWTwo--DeBeers Hands :30, 2008 (Box O3, Optical-disc RL00734-OP-0147)
  - JWTwo--Diageo Smirnoff Vodka Signature Conference Version, 2007 (Box O3, Optical-disc RL00734-OP-0148)